manufacturedirections.com 2013-09-25

# Privacy Policy - www.manufacturedirections.net

**Privacy Policy for www.manufacturedirections.net**

At www.manufacturedirections.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.manufacturedirections.net and how it is used. 

_Log Files_   
Like many other Web sites, www.manufacturedirections.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. _Cookies and Web Beacons_   
www.manufacturedirections.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. _DoubleClick DART Cookie_   
.:: Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to www.manufacturedirections.net.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.manufacturedirections.net and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page at - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.manufacturedirections.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.manufacturedirections.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of cookies. You may opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. If you have any question about our privacy policy then feel free to contact us so that we can discuss about it.
